http://www.judaicaemb.com/privacy.htm

Menu
Parochet - Ark CurtainsTorah Ark Curtains, Aron Kodesh Covers, Paroches
High Holidays Parochet
Modern Parochet
Traditional Parochet
View All
Torah Covers - Torah MantlesSefer Torah Mantels, Torah Scroll Covers, Velvet Torah Mantles
High Holiday Torah Covers
Modern Torah Covers
Traditional Torah Covers
View All
Torah Rollers - Atzei ChaimWooden Torah Handles & Plates, Eitz Chayim Torah set
Bimah Covers - Amud CoversBima Cover, Torah Reading Table Covers, Shtender Covers
Bein GavrahsFlat Torah Covers between Reading
Silver Torah OrnamentsTorah Breasplates, Torah Crown, Rimonim & Finials, Torah Cases, Torah Pointer / Yad, Torah Markers / Labels
View All
Torah Binders - GartlesTorah Belts, Torah Ties, Gartel for Sefer Torah
Tallit - Prayer ShawlsTallis, Talleisim, Tallitoth, Jewish Prayer Shawl
Tallit BagsVelvet Tallis & Tefillin Bags, Tallis Covers, Embroidered Tallit Covers
Kippot - YarmulkasSynagogue Kippot, Kippah, Yarmulkes, Womens Lace Headcovering
Chuppahs - Wedding CanopiesWedding Chuppahs, Tallit Chuppah
Judaica Gifts & AccessoriesJudaica & Gifts, Challah Covers, Shofars, Megillah Cases, Matzah Covers
Casket Covers
Parochet - Ark CurtainsTorah Ark Curtains, Aron Kodesh Covers, Paroches
High Holidays Parochet
Modern Parochet
Traditional Parochet
View All
Torah Covers - Torah MantlesSefer Torah Mantels, Torah Scroll Covers, Velvet Torah Mantles
High Holiday Torah Covers
Modern Torah Covers
Traditional Torah Covers
View All
Torah Rollers - Atzei ChaimWooden Torah Handles & Plates, Eitz Chayim Torah set
Bimah Covers - Amud CoversBima Cover, Torah Reading Table Covers, Shtender Covers
Bein GavrahsFlat Torah Covers between Reading
Silver Torah OrnamentsTorah Breasplates, Torah Crown, Rimonim & Finials, Torah Cases, Torah Pointer / Yad, Torah Markers / Labels
View All
Torah Binders - GartlesTorah Belts, Torah Ties, Gartel for Sefer Torah
Tallit - Prayer ShawlsTallis, Talleisim, Tallitoth, Jewish Prayer Shawl
Tallit BagsVelvet Tallis & Tefillin Bags, Tallis Covers, Embroidered Tallit Covers
Kippot - YarmulkasSynagogue Kippot, Kippah, Yarmulkes, Womens Lace Headcovering
Chuppahs - Wedding CanopiesWedding Chuppahs, Tallit Chuppah
Judaica Gifts & AccessoriesJudaica & Gifts, Challah Covers, Shofars, Megillah Cases, Matzah Covers
Privacy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
;To improve our website
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
;To improve customer service
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
;To process transactions
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
;To send periodic emails
The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at https://www.judaicaemb.com/termsofuse.htm
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on 2/8/2014
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
